We're on campus — here's a quick
snapshot.
of Syracuse Women’s Lacrosse in 2024.
Big picture — what stands out?
The team increased shot volume, averaging
about fifty-five shots per game,
but shooting efficiency fell. Goals per
game nudged up slightly
while assists per game dropped.
Who led the scoring in 2024? Emma Tyrrell
led the team —
sixty-one goals and thirty-one assists.
Any big year-over-year improvements? Yes —
Payton Rowley had the
biggest jump, a plus thirty-six increase.
What worrying trends should the coach fix?
Turnovers rose — they’re
up to about twenty-six point six per game.
Final coaching takeaway: Keep the
aggressive tempo,
but train shot selection and
decision-making.